Inventory of the Citizens for Reagan Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence (Folder 59)
  - John P. Sears correspondence (Folder 74)
    - Ohio, 1976 (Folder 79: 21)
    - Oklahoma, 1976 (Folder 79: 22)
    - Oregon, 1976 (Folder 79: 23)
    - Pennsylvania, 1976 (Folder 80: 1)
    - Rhode Island, 1976 (Folder 80: 2)
    - South Carolina, 1976 (Folder 80: 3)
    - South Dakota, 1976 (Folder 80: 4)
    - Tennessee, 1976 (Folder 80: 5)
    - Texas, 1976 (Folder 80: 6)
    - Utah, 1976 (Folder 80: 7)
    - Vermont, 1976 (Folder 80: 8)
    - Virginia, 1976 (Folder 80: 9)
    - Washington, 1976 (Folder 80: 10)
    - Washington, D.C., 1976 (Folder 80: 11)
    - West Virginia, 1976 (Folder 80: 12)
    - Wisconsin, 1976 (Folder 80: 13)
    - Wyoming, 1976 (Folder 80: 14)
    - Foreign Countries - Balboa and Gamboa in Canal Zone, Guam, and Sweden, 1976 (Folder 80: 15)
  - John P. Sears thank-you letters for contribution, 1976 (Folder 81)
    - Alabama (Folder 81: 1)
    - Arizona (Folder 81: 2)
    - Arkansas (Folder 81: 3)
    - California (Folder 81: 4-6)
    - Colorado (Folder 81: 7)
    - Connecticut (Folder 81: 8)
    - Delaware (Folder 81: 9)
    - District of Columbia (Folder 81: 10)
    - Florida (Folder 81: 11)
    - Georgia (Folder 81: 12)
    - Hawaii (Folder 81: 13)
    - Idaho (Folder 81: 14)
    - Illinois (Folder 81: 15)
    - Indiana (Folder 82: 1)
    - Iowa (Folder 82: 2)
    - Kansas (Folder 82: 3)
    - Kentucky (Folder 82: 4)
    - Louisiana (Folder 82: 5)
    - Maine (Folder 82: 6)
    - Maryland (Folder 82: 7)
    - Massachusetts (Folder 82: 8)
    - Michigan (Folder 82: 9)
    - Minnesota (Folder 82: 10)
    - Mississippi (Folder 82: 11)
    - Missouri (Folder 82: 12)
    - Montana (Folder 82: 13)
    - Nebraska (Folder 82: 14)
    - Nevada (Folder 82: 15)
    - New Hampshire (Folder 82: 16)
    - New Jersey (Folder 82: 17)
    - New Mexico (Folder 82: 18)
    - New York (Folder 82: 19)
    - North Carolina (Folder 82: 20)
    - North Dakota (Folder 82: 21)
    - Ohio (Folder 82: 22)
    - Oklahoma (Folder 82: 23)
    - Oregon (Folder 82: 24)
    - Pennsylvania (Folder 82: 25)
    - Rhode Island (Folder 82: 26)
    - South Carolina (Folder 82: 27)
    - South Dakota (Folder 82: 28)
    - Tennessee (Folder 82: 29)
    - Texas (Folder 83: 1-2)
    - Utah (Folder 83: 3)
    - Vermont (Folder 83: 4)
    - Virginia (Folder 83: 5)
    - Washington (Folder 83: 6)
    - West Virginia (Folder 83: 7)
    - Wisconsin (Folder 83: 8)
  - Common Cause - Letters in response to a questionnaire, 1975-1976 (Folder 84: 1)
  - Support letters (Folder 84)
    - undated (Folder 84: 2)
    - Foreign - Australia, Germany, Honduras, Mexico, and Taiwan, 1975-1976 (Folder 84: 3)
    - July, 1975 (Folder 84: 4-5)
    - August, 1975 (Folder 84: 6-7)
    - September, 1975 (Folder 84: 8-9)
    - October, 1975 (Folder 85: 1-2)
    - November, 1975 (Folder 85: 3-4)
    - December, 1975 (Folder 85: 5)
    - Thomas A. Malatesta responses (Folder 85)
      - July, 1975-1976 (Folder 85: 6)
      - August, 1975-1976 (Folder 85: 7)
      - September, 1975-1976 (Folder 85: 8)
      - October, 1975-1976 (Folder 85: 9)
      - November, 1975-1976 (Folder 86: 1)
      - December, 1975-1976 (Folder 86: 2)
      - undated (Folder 86: 3)
      - 1975-1976 (Folder 86: 4)
  - John P. Sears/Ronald Reagan correspondence, 1976 September-October (Box-folder 87)
    - Alabama (Folder 87: 1)
    - Arizona (Folder 87: 2)
    - Arkansas (Folder 87: 3)
    - California (Folder 87: 4)
    - Connecticut (Folder 87: 5)
    - Florida (Folder 87: 6)
    - Georgia (Folder 87: 7)
    - Illinois (Folder 87: 8)
    - Maine (Folder 87: 9)
    - Maryland (Folder 87: 10)
    - Massachusetts (Folder 87: 11)
    - Minnesota (Folder 87: 12)
    - Missouri (Folder 87: 13)
    - Mississippi (Folder 87: 14)
    - Montana (Folder 87: 15)
    - Nevada (Folder 87: 16)
    - New Hampshire (Folder 87: 17)
    - New Jersey (Folder 87: 18)
    - New Mexico (Folder 87: 19)
    - New York (Folder 87: 20)
    - North Carolina (Folder 87: 21)
    - Ohio (Folder 87: 22)
    - Oklahoma (Folder 87: 23)
    - Oregon (Folder 87: 24)
    - Pennsylvania (Folder 87: 25)
    - South Carolina (Folder 87: 26)
    - South Dakota (Folder 87: 27)
    - Tennessee (Folder 87: 28)
    - Texas (Folder 87: 29)
    - Utah (Folder 87: 30)
    - Vermont (Folder 87: 31)
    - Washington (Folder 87: 32)
    - Washington, D.C. (Folder 87: 33)
    - West Virginia (Folder 87: 34)
    - Wisconsin (Folder 87: 35)
    - Wyoming (Folder 87: 36)
  - Post-Convention correspondence unanswered, 1976 (Folder 87: 37)
  - California: John P. Sears correspondence, 1976 May-August (Folder 87: 38)
  - John P. Sears outgoing correspondence, 1975-1976 (Folder 88:)
    - Iowa (Folder 88: 1)
    - Kansas (Folder 88: 2)
    - Kentucky (Folder 88: 3)
    - Louisiana (Folder 88: 4)
    - Maine (Folder 88: 5)
    - Maryland (Folder 88: 6-7)
    - Maryland (Folder 89: 1)
    - Massachusetts (Folder 89: 2)
    - Mexico (Folder 89: 3)
    - Michigan (Folder 89: 4)
    - Minnesota (Folder 89: 5)
    - Mississippi (Folder 89: 6)
    - Missouri (Folder 89: 7)
    - Montana (Folder 89: 8)
    - Nebraska (Folder 89: 9)
    - Nevada (Folder 89: 10)
    - New Hampshire (Folder 89: 11)
    - New Jersey (Folder 89: 12)
    - Georgia (Folder 89: 13)
    - Guam (Folder 89: 14)
    - Hawaii (Folder 89: 15)
    - Idaho (Folder 89: 16)
    - Illinois (Folder 89: 17)
    - Indiana (Folder 89: 18)
  - John P. Sears correspondence, 1976 (Folder 90:)
    - Arizona (Folder 90: 1)
    - Hawaii (Folder 90: 2)
    - Massachusetts (Folder 90: 3)
    - North Dakota (Folder 90: 4)
    - Rhode Island (Folder 90: 5)
    - South Dakota (Folder 90: 6)
    - Utah (Folder 90: 7)
    - Vermont (Folder 90: 8)
    - Virginia (Folder 90: 9)
    - Washington (Folder 90: 10)
    - West Virginia (Folder 90: 11)
    - Wisconsin (Folder 90: 12)
    - Wyoming (Folder 90: 13)
    - Overseas correspondence (Folder 90: 14)
  - David A. Keene correspondence, 1976 May-July (Folder 91: 1)
  - Jim Lake correspondence, 1976 June (Folder 91: 2)
  - John P. Magnotti correspondence (Folder 91:)
    - February, 1976 (Folder 91: 3-4)
    - March, 1976 (Folder 91: 5)
    - March-April, 1976 (Folder 91: 6)
    - April. Includes 3 photographic prints depicting Buddy Ring, Cindy Lynn, and 2 unidentified women, undated, 1976 (Folder 91: 7)
- Ronald Reagan speech schedules and correspondence, 1975 (Folder 92:)
  - Texas manufacturing Association, Dallas, Texas, January 14 (Folder 92: 1)
  - Chamber of Commerce, San Antonio, Texas, January 15 (Folder 92: 2)
  - Printing Industry of Nashville, Tennessee, January 16 (Folder 92: 3)
  - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tennessee, January 16 (Folder 92: 4)
  - Richmond Public Forum, Richmond, Virginia, January 17 (Folder 92: 5)
  - International Safari Club, Las Vegas, Nevada, January 30 (Folder 92: 6)
  - American Cattlemen's Association, Las Vegas, Nevada, January 31 (Folder 92: 7)
  - American Dehydrators, San Diego, California, February 5 (Folder 92: 8)
  - Health Industry Manufacturing Association, San Diego, California, February 5 (Folder 92: 9)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Grand Island, Nebraska, February 14 (Folder 92: 10)
  - American Conservative Union, Washington, D.C., February 15 (Folder 92: 11)
  - GOP Fundraiser, Congressional Country Club, Maryland, February 16 (Folder 92: 12)
  - Tazewell County Republicans, Pekin, Illinois, February 17 (Folder 92: 13)
  - O'Hare Executive Club, Chicago, Illinois, February 18 (Folder 92: 14)
  - GOP Fundraiser, Clark County, Las Vegas, Nevada, February 18 (Folder 92: 15)
  - Intermountain Oil Marketers Convention, Las Vegas, Nevada, February 19 (Folder 92: 16)
  - Sales and Marketing Executives of Fort Worth, Texas, February 26 (Folder 92: 17)
  - Monroe Chamber of Commerce, Louisiana, February 27 (Folder 92: 18)
  - American Concrete Pipe Association, Boca Raton, Florida, March 17 (Folder 92: 19)
  - Lake County GOP Fundraiser, Jacksonville, Florida, March 17 (Folder 92: 20)
  - GOP Fundraiser, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, March 18 (Folder 92: 21)
  - John Ericcson League, Oakbrook, Illinois, March 19 (Folder 92: 22)
  - Charles Edison Forum, St. Louis, Missouri, March 20 (Folder 92: 23)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Cullman, Alabama, March 21 (Folder 92: 24)
  - Trunk and Tusk, Phoenix, Arizona, March 25 (Folder 92: 25)
  - The Pilgrims, London, England, April 5-9 (Folder 92: 26)
  - Seaver College Dedication, Malibu, California, April 20 (Folder 92: 27)
  - United Airlines Dinner, Los Angeles, California, April 23 (Folder 92: 28)
  - Iowa Young Republicans, Des Moines, Iowa, April 25 (Folder 93: 1)
  - Friends of Dan Murphy, Southfield, Michigan, April 26 (Folder 93: 2)
  - New Jersey GOP, Paramus, New Jersey, April 27 (Folder 93: 3)
  - Mississippi State College, Jackson, Mississippi, April 28 (Folder 93: 4)
  - Mississippi GOP, Jackson, Mississippi, April 28 (Folder 93: 5)
  - Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association, Boca Raton, Florida, April 29 (Folder 93: 6)
  - Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta, Georgia, April 29 (Folder 93: 7)
  - Atlas Van Lines Traffic Forum, Chicago, Illinois, May 7 (Folder 93: 8)
  - Fundraiser for Phil Crane, Chicago, Illinois, May 7 (Folder 93: 9)
  - Fundraiser for Gene Taylor, Springfield, Missour, May 8 (Folder 93: 10)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Tucson, Arizona, May 14 (Folder 93: 11)
  - Sales and Marketing Executives, Houston, Texas, May 28 (Folder 93: 12)
  - Middlesex County GOP, Boston, Massachusetts, May 30 (Folder 93: 13)
  - GOP Fundraiser (three counties), West Virginia, May 29 (Folder 93: 14)
  - Georgia State Republican Convention, Atlanta, Georgia, May 31 (Folder 93: 15)
  - National Headliner Awards, Atlantic City, New Jersey, May 31 (Folder 93: 16)
  - Reader's Digest, Pleasantville, New York, June 17 (Folder 93: 17)
  - National Federation of Independent Business, Washington, D.C., June 17 (Folder 93: 18)
  - Business/Professional Advertising Association, Pittsburg, Pennsylvania, June 18 (Folder 93: 19)
  - Fundraiser for Alvin Katz, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, June 18 (Folder 93: 20)
  - Indiana GOP Fundraiser, Indianapolis, Indiana, June 19 (Folder 93: 21)
  - Texas Society of Certified Public Accountants, El Paso, Texas, June 20 (Folder 93: 22)
  - Texas GOP Fundraiser, Dallas, Texas, June 20 (Folder 93: 23)
  - Texas GOP, Beaumont, Texas, June 21 (Folder 93: 24)
  - P.O.W. Reunion, San Antonio, Texas, June 28 (Folder 93: 25)
  - Ronald Reagan's trip (Montana, North Carolina, North Dakota, South Dakota, Virginia, and Washington) (Folder 94: 1)
  - Young Republican National Convention, Indianapolis, Indiana, July 2 (Folder 94: 2)
  - Washington GOP, Tacoma, Washington, July 20 (Folder 94: 3)
  - Montana GOP, Bozeman, Montana, July 21 (Folder 94: 4)
  - North Dakota GOP, Minot, North Dakota, July 22 (Folder 94: 5)
  - South Dakota GOP, Rapid City, South Dakota, July 23 (Folder 94: 6)
  - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, Shenandoah Valley, Virginia, July 24 (Folder 94: 7)
  - North Carolina Congressional Club, Raleigh, North Carolina, July 25 (Folder 94: 8)
  - National Retail Hardware Association, San Diego, California, July 31 (Folder 94: 9)
  - Society of Professional Journalists, Los Angeles, California, August 18 (Folder 94: 10)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, Los Angeles, California, August 18 (Folder 94: 11)
  - Westside Republican Council, Los Angeles, California, September 7 (Folder 94: 12)
  - Hoover symposium, Washington, D.C., September 11 (Folder 94: 13)
  - The Charles Edison Memorial Youth Fund, Washington, D.C., September 12 (Folder 94: 14)
  - New Hampshire, September, undated (Folder 94: 15)
  - National Federation Republic Women, Dallas, Texas, September 12 (Folder 94: 16)
  - Amway, Charlotte, North Carolina, September 13 (Folder 94: 17)
  - South Central Illinois GOP, Robinson, Illinois, September 22 (Folder 94: 18)
  - National Association of Convenience Stores, Las Vegas, Nevada, September 22 (Folder 94: 19)
  - Alabama Business Hall of Fame, Tuscaloosa, Alabama, September 23 (Folder 94: 20)
  - Edison Fund, Atlanta, Georgia, September 24 (Folder 94: 21)
  - Tennessee GOP Capital Club, Memphis, Tennessee, September 24 (Folder 94: 22)
  - Montgomery County GOP, Dayton, Ohio, September 25 (Folder 94: 23)
  - National Office Products Association, Chicago, Illinois, September 26 (Folder 94: 24)
  - Executive Club of Chicago, Illinois, September 26 (Folder 94: 25)
  - Bank Marketing Association, Las Vegas, Nevada, September 29 (Folder 94: 26)
  - Alumni lunch, Sacramento, California, October 1 (Folder 95: 1)
  - Western States Republican Conference, Portland, Oregon, October 3 (Folder 95: 2)
  - California Republican Assembly Convention, Palm Springs, California, October 3 (Folder 95: 3)
  - Douglas County GOP Fundraiser, Lake Tahoe, California, October 5 (Folder 95: 4)
  - Reno Philharmonic Symphony Association, Reno, Nevada, October 5 (Folder 95: 5)
  - Reception for Congressman Bud Shuster, Altoona, Pennsylvania, October 6 (Folder 95: 6)
  - Maryland State Chamber of Commerce, Bedford Springs, Pennsylvania, October 6 (Folder 95: 7)
  - Town Hall of Cleveland, Cleveland, Ohio, October 7 (Folder 95: 8)
  - St. Joseph Building Fund Dinner, Houston, Texas, October 7 (Folder 95: 9)
  - National Hardware Convention, San Francisco, California, October 8 (Folder 95: 10)
  - Alumni lunch, San Francisco, California, October 8 (Folder 95: 11)
  - Fundraiser for Forty Four Assembly District, Los Angeles, California, October 12 (Folder 95: 12)
  - American Conservative Union Reception, Los Angeles, California, October 14 (Folder 95: 13)
  - Junior League of Los Angeles, California, October 15 (Folder 95: 14)
  - Biennial Convention California Republican Convention, Los Angeles, California, October 15 (Folder 95: 15)
  - New York Conservative Party, New York City, New York, October 20 (Folder 95: 16)
  - World Affairs, Council of Philadelphia, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, October 21 (Folder 95: 17)
  - Yale Political Union, New Haven, Connecticut, October 21 (Folder 95: 18)
  - Suffolk County GOP, New York City, New York, October 22 (Folder 95: 19)
  - Fundraiser for Congressman Tom Hagedorn, Mankato, Minnesota, October 23 (Folder 95: 20)
  - St. Paul Grand Old Party (GOP), St. Paul, Minnesota, October 23 (Folder 95: 21)
  - Association of Commerce and Industry, Albuquerque, New Mexico, October 24 (Folder 95: 22)
  - National Welding Supply Association, San Francisco, California, October, 30 (Folder 95: 23)
  - American Broadcasting Company, New York City, New York, October, undated (Folder 96: 1)
  - Disney lunch, October, undated (Folder 96: 2)
  - Florida GOP, Boca Raton, Florida, November 3 (Folder 96: 3)
  - Florida GOP, Clearwater, Florida, November 4 (Folder 96: 4)
  - Association of Builders and Contractors, Houston, Texas, November 14 (Folder 96: 5)
  - Oklahoma GOP, Tulsa, Oklahoma, November 14 (Folder 96: 6)
  - Oklahoma Hall of Fame, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, November 15 (Folder 96: 7)
  - International Sanitary Supply Association, Chicago, Illinois, November 16 (Folder 96: 8)
  - Twentieth Anniversary of National Review, New York, November 17 (Folder 96: 9)
  - Investment officers, New York City, New York, November 17 (Folder 96: 10)
  - Woman's Forum, Wichita Falls, Texas, November 18 (Folder 96: 11)
  - National Soft Drink Association, Dallas, Texas, November 19 (Folder 96: 12)
  - Oregon GOP, Eugene, Oregon, December 1 (Folder 96: 13)
  - Nebraska GOP, Omaha, Nebraska, December 2 (Folder 96: 14)
  - Congressman Ed Young Fundraiser, Florence, South Carolina, December 8 (Folder 96: 15)
  - Alexandria Chamber of Commerce, Alexandria, Louisiana, December 9 (Folder 96: 16)
  - Lafayette Chamber of Commerce, Lafayette, Louisiana, December 9 (Folder 96: 17)
  - American Hotel and Motel Association, Los Angeles, California, December 11 (Folder 96: 18)
  - Orange County Republican Women, Newport Beach, California, December 11 (Folder 96: 19)
  - Orange County Fundraiser, Anaheim, California, December 11 (Folder 96: 20)
  - Southern Republican Conference, Houston, Texas, December 13 (Folder 96: 21)
- Volunteers, binder, 1975-1976 (Folder 97: 1)
- Mayors of America's principal cities, 1978 July (Folder 98: 1)
- Local party leaders, 1976-1978 (Folder 98: 2-3)
- 1976 primary results (Folder 98: 4)
- Black Republicans, undated (Folder 98: 5)
- Delegates, 1968 and 1972 (Folder 98: 6)
- Elected Republicans, 1977-1978 (Folder 99: 1-4)
- Elected Republicans, 1978 (Folder 100: 1-4)
- Position papers, 1976 (Folder 101: 1)
- Correspondence
  - General, 1975 (Folder 101: 2)
  - January-February, 1976 (Folder 101: 3)
  - March-June, 1976 (Folder 101: 4)
  - June-August, 1976 (Folder 101: 5)
  - September-December, 1976 (Folder 101: 6)
- About the press, 1976 (Folder 102: 1)
- Press releases, 1975-1976 (Folder 102: 2)
- Instructions to advance personnel, undated (Folder 102: 3)
- Announcement, 1975 (Folder 102: 4)
- Charles Martin and Associates, 1976 (Folder 102: 5)
- Clippings - Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Folder 102: 6-7)
- Convention/Delegates, 1975-1976 (Folder 102: 8)
- Conventions/Miscellaneous, 1976 (Folder 102: 9)
- Election Law, 1975-1976 (Folder 102: 10)
- Gerald Ford et al, 1976 (Folder 102: 11)
- Issues - Ronald Reagan, 1976 (Folder 102: 12)
- Media, 1975-1976 (Folder 102: 13)
- Polls, 1975 (Folder 102: 14)
- Primary states, 1976 (Folder 102: 15)
- Republican National Convention Task Force, 1976 (Folder 103: 1)
- Reagan personal, 1976 (Folder 103: 2)
- Ronald Reagan's record, 1974-1976 (Folder 103: 3)
- Schedule, 1976 (Folder 103: 4)
- Senator Richard Schweiker, 1964-1976 (Folder 103: 5)
- Campaign speeches, 1975-1976 (Folder 103: 6)
- Staff, 1975-1976 (Folder 103: 7)
- Transfer proposal (90 billion), 1975-1976 (Folder 103: 8)
- United Republicans of California (UROC) resolution, 1975 (Folder 103: 9)
- Speeches of Ronald Reagan, 1976 (Folder 104: 1)
- Convention speech, 1976 August (Folder 104: 2)
- Transcript of Meet the Press, 1 May 1977 (Folder 104: 3)
- Speeches, 1977-1979 (Folder 104: 4-6)
- Radio transcripts, 1976 and 1978 (Folder 104: 7-8)
- Radio transcripts, 1979 (Folder 105: 1-3)
- Columns, 1977-1978 (Folder 105: 4-6)
- Ronald Reagan, 1978-1979 November (Folder 106: 1)
- Radio stations with Ronald Reagan broadcasts and newspapers with his columns, 1976-1978 (Folder 106: 2)
- Ronald Reagan biographies, 1967-1979 and undated (Folder 106: 3)
- Ronald Reagan record and position papers, 1974-1979 (Folder 106: 4)
- Ronald Reagan columns and extra copies, 1979 (Folder 106: 5-6)
- Clippings and position papers (Folder 107:)
  - 1979 November - 1980 Spring (Folder 107: 1)
  - 1980 March-April (Folder 107: 2)
  - 1980 (Folder 107: 3)
  - 1980 position papers (Folder 107: 4)
- 1976 schedules (Folder 108: 1-2)
- Speeches, statements, press releases, and press manifesto, 1976 (Folder 108: 3)
- Miscellany, 1976 (Folder 108: 4)
- 1976 schedules (Folder 108: 1-2)
- Speeches, statements, press releases, and press manifesto, 1976 (Folder 108: 3)
- Miscellany, 1976 (Folder 108: 4)
- Thank you letters list, 1976 (Folder 108: 5)
- Staff names, undated (Folder 108: 6)
- Organizational chart, June 1976 (Folder 108: 7)
- Operation Wind-up, 1976 (Folder 108: 8)
- Citizens for the Republic (CFTR) newsletters, 1979 (Folder 109: 1)
- Citizens for the Republic (CFTR) newsletters, 1980-1986 (Folder 109: 2-3)
- National Citizens for Reagan, Washington, D.C. - Ronald Reagan's announcement trip to Washington, D.C., Florida, New Hampshire, North Carolina, Illinois, and California, 1975 November 20 and 21. Detailed schedule (Folder 109: 4)
- Closed - Financial records, campaign contributions (Folder 110-111)
- Audio-video campaign materials, 1975-1976 (Folder On shelf)
  - 30-60 second statements on 2 inch videotapes (Folder On shelf)
    - Defense, 1976 January 22, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      Scope and Contents note
      This ad opens with an unidentified man in the audience asking Reagan about cuts in defense spending. From the podium, Reagan tells the audience that the US must never be second to anyone else in the world in military power. This television commercial for the 1976 Ronald Reagan presidential campaign aired around January 22, 1976.
      Sequence: Slate (00:26), opens to audience member asking question (00:37). Dropout and banding as on original tape.
    - Government, 1976 January 22, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      While Reagan steps to the podium a narrator provides an introduction, stating that Reagan recently gave a group of citizens his views on the role of government. Speaking to the audience, Reagan declares that Washington politicians are slow to catch on to the reawakening of the American spirit of independence and self reliance. He calls for a government that's confident in what people can do for themselves. This television commercial for the 1976 Ronald Reagan presidential campaign aired around January 22, 1976.
      Sequence: Slate (00:34), Reagan steps to podium as narration begins (00:44). Audible edge damage on the audio track.
    - Gun Control, 1976 January 22, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      This is an excerpt from a live audience event with Reagan at the podium. An unidentified woman in the audience asks a question about gun control, and Reagan replies. He does not wish to disarm honest citizens and leave the others armed.
      Sequence: Slate (00:35), woman asks question and Reagan replies (00:47), "Reagan" slate (01:11), black (01:18).
    - Inflation, 1976 January 22, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      This ad opens to Reagan speaking to an audience. After pointing to years of runaway inflation, he calls for the federal government to balance the budget so that people will know that a dollar next month will buy as much as it did last month. This television commercial for the 1976 Ronald Reagan presidential campaign aired around January 22, 1976.
      Sequence: Slate (00:56), Reagan at podium (01:06).
    - Social Security, 1976 January 22, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      This ad opens to an audience listening to Ronald Reagan, who talks from the stage about Social Security. He asserts that any reform to the program must have as its first priority a guarantee that those who depend on Social Security will continue to receive monthly benefits that keep pace with inflation. He goes on to call for a balanced budget. This television commercial for the 1976 Ronald Reagan presidential campaign aired around January 22, 1976.
      Sequence: Slate (00:47), opens to audience listening to Reagan (01:00). Lines of dropout in image due to scratches on original tape.
    - Taxes, 1976 January 22, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
      As Ronald Reagan covers a smile and steps away from the podium a narrator announces that this happened at one of Reagan's citizen press conferences. A boy in the audience says that he thinks taxes should be lower because the money doesn't got to good use. Back at the podium, Reagan tells the boy he's talking sense, and that government at all levels takes too great a percentage of people's earnings. This television commercial for the 1976 Ronald Reagan presidential campaign aired around January 22, 1976.
      Sequence: Slate (00:49), opens to Reagan covering a smile on stage (01:02).
    - Unemployment, 1976 January 22, 30 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)
    - Unemployment, 1976 January 22, 60 seconds, 1 videotape (Folder On shelf)